tias.com 2014-06-30

# TIAS Privacy Statement

**Privacy Policy**

This site is maintained and operated by TIAS.COM, Inc. ('TIAS'). TIAS.com is now the largest "fixed price" source of antiques and collectibles on the Internet, serving over 120 million page views per month. We host approximately 1,000 online antique and collectible merchants and offer a variety of services for collectors and hobbyists -- among them free virtual antique cards, free newsletters, low-cost classified ads and discussion groups.

On some TIAS web pages, you can make requests, purchase products or ask to receive materials. On these pages, we collect your name and contact information. In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding yourself, your experience with our products and services, and your contact preferences. TIAS is committed to respecting your privacy.  Once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your customer relationship with TIAS and our merchants. 

This statement regarding the privacy of the information you provide online covers five main areas: Awareness, Choice, Access & Accuracy, Security, and Oversight.

**Awareness**  
TIAS provides this Online Privacy Statement to make you aware of our privacy policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**How we use it**  
TIAS uses your information to better understand your needs and to provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, to communicate back to you, to update you on services, products and benefits, and to personalize our web site for you.

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest.

**Who we share it with**  
TIAS will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the data you provide online with other TIAS entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf to complete the activities described above. Such TIAS entities and/or business partners, including those located in other countries, are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data. To grant or deny permission to share your information with others, click [here](http://www.tias.com/mytias/) (this feature allows you to review all mailing lists on our site and remove yourself if you wish) or contact [postmaster@tias.com](mailto:postmaster@tias.com)

**Choice**  
TIAS will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without letting you know and offering you a choice.

If you wish to have your personally identifiable information removed from our system, you can do so by clicking [here](http://www.tias.com/mytias/) or by contacting us at [postmaster@tias.com](mailto:postmaster@tias.com) and asking to be removed from our mailing list.

If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email. 

If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to [abuse@tias.com](mailto:abuse@tias.com) for review. 

**Access & Accuracy**  
TIAS strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate.  If you wish to correct your information, you may correct it yourself by clicking [here](http://www.tias.com/mytias/) or by contacting us at [postmaster@tias.com](mailto:postmaster@tias.com?subject=Corrected%20Personal%20Information)  with corrected information.

You can review and change your current mailing lists and personal information at any time by clicking [here](http://www.tias.com/mytias/).

TIAS is committed to honoring your intellectual property rights. If you believe that these rights have been violated by any TIAS merchant, please contact us at [privacy@tias.com](mailto:privacy@tias.com?subject=Intellectual%20Property%20Ownership) and provide the details of the infringement.

**Security**  
TIAS is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Read about why your order data is secure at TIAS.

While you are shopping at TIAS, we may place a temporary cookie on your computer system.    We use the cookie for two purposes: to keep track of the number of users accessing our site and for keeping track of your shopping carts.   The only time we use cookies to correlate with names is to tie the items ordered to the name of the person doing the ordering in our shopping cart application. Cookies are the most reliable and easiest to implement way of doing this.  We do not share our cookies with other sites, nor do we use cookies from other sites and when you close your browser, the TIAS cookie will automatically be deleted.  Click here for a full explanation of our cookie processing.

**Oversight**  
If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy,  you can contact us:

| 

**E-mail:**

| 

---|---  
  
**U.S. mail:**

| 

16 Heath Place  
Garden City, NY 11530  
  
**Telephone:**

| 

1-888-OLD-STUFF
